export const dashboardFlow = [
    {
        user: { fullName: 'Jack Sparrow', link: 'sparrow_link' },
        package: {
            title: 'Angol',
            words: [
                { front: 'kitchen', back: 'konyha', correct: 'correct' },
                { front: 'dog', back: 'kutya', correct: 'incorrect' },
                { front: 'monitor', back: 'kepernyo', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'watr', back: 'viz', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'paper', back: 'papir', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'desk', back: 'asztal', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'jar', back: 'csesze', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'door', back: 'ajto', correct: 'unknown' },
            ],
            approved: false,
        },
    },
    {
        user: { fullName: 'Jack Sparrow', link: 'sparrow_link' },
        package: {
            title: 'Angol',
            words: [
                { front: 'kitchen', back: 'konyha', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'dog', back: 'kutya', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'monitor', back: 'kepernyo', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'watr', back: 'viz', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'paper', back: 'papir', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'desk', back: 'asztal', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'jar', back: 'csesze', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'door', back: 'ajto', correct: 'unknown' },
            ],
            approved: false,
        },
    },
    {
        user: { fullName: 'Jack Sparrow', link: 'sparrow_link' },
        package: {
            title: 'Angol',
            words: [
                { front: 'kitchen', back: 'konyha', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'dog', back: 'kutya', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'monitor', back: 'kepernyo', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'watr', back: 'viz', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'paper', back: 'papir', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'desk', back: 'asztal', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'jar', back: 'csesze', correct: 'unknown' },
                { front: 'door', back: 'ajto', correct: 'unknown' },
            ],
            approved: false,
        },
    },
];
